{
    "subject": "resource/Charlene_(song)",
    "predicate": "ontology/album",
    "object": "resource/Comin'_from_Where_I'm_From",
    "human_readable": "Charlene is part of the album Comin' from Where I'm From.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9119467735290527,
            "question": "Where can I find more information about Charlene and 'Comin' from Where I'm From'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8957443237304688,
            "question": "What album is Charlene part of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7215316891670227,
            "question": "What is Charlene known for besides being part of this album?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.646530032157898,
            "question": "What is the name of the album Charlene is featured on?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5981854200363159,
            "question": "Is there a specific theme or story behind 'Comin' from Where I'm From'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5765942335128784,
            "question": "Is Charlene a musician?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5188744068145752,
            "question": "Do you know the year 'Comin' from Where I'm From' was released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4527302384376526,
            "question": "Can you list any other artists featured on 'Comin' from Where I'm From'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44386225938796997,
            "question": "What genre of music might 'Comin' from Where I'm From' belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4052395522594452,
            "question": "Has Charlene released any other music?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Charlene is part of the album Comin' from Where I'm From.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1181_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre of music might 'Comin' from Where I'm From' belong to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1181_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you list any other artists featured on 'Comin' from Where I'm From'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1181_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Do you know the year 'Comin' from Where I'm From' was released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1181_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1181_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1181_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1181_119.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1181_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1181_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1181_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1181_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1181_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1181_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1181_81.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I can conclude that:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents confirm that \"Charlene\" is a song by Anthony Hamilton and it is indeed part of his album \"Comin' from Where I'm From\", released in 2003."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that \"Charlene\" is a song by Anthony Hamilton, released in his second studio album titled \"Comin' from Where I\u2019m From.\" Therefore, the triple \"Charlene is part of the album Comin' From Where I'm From\" is supported by the provided context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}